Chu Qingyun,
My Lady, you are...
It's me,
Xue Keying,
the Second Miss of the Duke
of Ying's Mansion,
Xue Ruowan's sister.
As far as I know,
the Duke of Ying only has one daughter
named Xue Ruowan.
I have never heard of
her having a sister.
How could this be?
There is no such person as Xue Keying.
Then who am I?
Don't block our General's way.
Ning Yuanci!
I'm so glad you're alive.
How audacious!
How dare you call our General by his name!
Don't you recognize me either?
Cui Hu!
Tonight's engagement banquet
is very important.
There can't be any mistakes.
Throw all irrelevant people
out.
Yes, sir.
Move.
Stop!
Let her go.
General Ning,
Judging by her clothes,
she should be a maid of our family.
I hope the General won't
make things difficult for her.
In that case...
I shall grant Miss Xue this favor.
Thank you, General.
Let's go.
Tonight, Xue Shiyan
will poison Xue Ruowan.
But without Xue Keying,
who can save her?
No.
I must stop this.
I will make Ning Yuanci
see Xue Shiyan's true colors.
This is Miss Xue's favorite.
Remember to serve it to the main table.
Okay.
Give this to me.
Xiaofu.
So I do have a name.
Didn't you already
give me the medicine?
What do you want me to do now?
Medicine?
What medicine?
She'll only get a little sick
if she eats it.
When the time comes, insist
that Ning Yuanci did it.
Don't forget
who holds
the lives of your whole family.
Be a good girl.
Where is the medicine I gave you?
You didn't already
give it to Xue Ruowan, did you?
If
Xue Ruowan takes this medicine,
it won't just be a minor illness.
She will die.
How could the Duke poison
his own daughter?
It's all Xue Shiyan's
deceptive rhetoric.
If you believe Xue Shiyan,
he will have leverage over you,
and there will be no turning back.
Then what should I do?
How can I
protect my lady?
Although we are not
the protagonists of the story,
we are not
puppets to be manipulated.
As long as we truly live,
we should become
who we want to be.
Wan'er said she was going out
for some fresh air.
Why hasn't she returned yet?
General,
we found an assassin.
We await your orders, My Lord.
Didn't you say
you had something urgent to tell me?
What is it?
What?
Who told you that?
There is no time to explain.
Young Master Chu
will be waiting for you
outside Jinming Pool.
My Lady,
you should leave the city with him
tonight.
This maid turned herself in.
You said you are a spy
for the Duke of Ying
and know where the evidence
of his treason is.
Why should I believe you?
In the Battle of Heishui River
five years ago,
your entire family was murdered
because Xue Shiyan colluded
with Northern spies.
The secret code he used to communicate
with the spies
was the deer totem.
Who exactly are you?
Where exactly is the evidence
of Xue Shiyan's crimes?
I can tell you,
but you must let Xue Ruowan go
and guarantee her safety.
Do you think I want
to listen to your nonsense?
Do you think I won't kill you?
If you kill me,
you will get nothing.
Don't
you want
the murderer of your entire family
to pay the price?
Men!
Pass on my orders
to search the entire city.
What happened?
Where is my daughter?
Northern assassins
have kidnapped Xue Ruowan.
I have ordered a city-wide search.
To prevent the assassins
from escaping in the chaos,
no one in Jinming Pool
is allowed to leave tonight.
What?
My daughter is missing!
And you still want to trap me here?
Ning Yuanci!
What are you trying to do?
Ning Yuanci,
you accuse me of treason.
Do you have any proof?
Don't be hasty.
The evidence will be here shortly.
General,
these were all found
in the Duke of Ying's storehouse.
These are the paintings
he used to pass intelligence to the spies.
The totem messages are hidden
beneath the canvas.
My father
treated you like a brother,
but you harbored resentment,
committing treason
just to wipe out my entire family.
You.
The Xue family has held a noble title
for three generations.
I have served two emperors.
How dare you touch me?
I will not let you
die so easily.
I will chop off
all your hands,
stuff your body
into a tiny box,
and sink it into the sea.
She said I'm a spy.
I could also say
she was bribed by you.
I know her background better than you do.
I have plenty of ways to prove
she belongs to your residence.
Her testimony is invalid.
Now that so much evidence
has been found in your residence,
even without her,
I can still convict you.
Ning Yuanci,
w-what are you doing?
Y-You
wouldn't dare kill her.
Are you feeling guilty?
You colluded
to frame me.
Her testimony is not credible.
Then my testimony
should be credible, right?
Xue Ruowan,
didn't I ask Chu Qingyun
to take you away?
Why are you back?
Five years ago,
my mother found letters
between Xue Shiyan and the enemy.
She was dying at the time,
so she left me this painting.
I originally thought
she just wanted to leave me a memento.
Until this painting
was accidentally roasted by fire,
I found my mother's
last words to me on it.
It recorded
the hiding places of all the letters.
The truth will be known
once investigated.
Let's go.
General Ning,
this is what the Xue family owes you.
From now on,
let's go our separate ways.
This should
count as a happy ending, right?
But why don't I
feel happy at all?
Ning
Yuanci!
Why am I
back here again?
Didn't we agree
that you'd let me go back
after the happy ending?
Let me out!
Xue Keying,
the actress Xia Yimo has returned
to her world.
And you must stay here
to accept your fate.
An accident occurred
on the first day of shooting
the costume drama Moxiang.
Fans question the crew's
inadequate first aid measures.
Top actress acts like a diva on set.
Drowning and falling into a coma
caused the crew to shut down.
Rumor has it that Xia Yimo
pushed Sun Xiaofei first.
She's so vicious.
Now she's tasting her own medicine.
Support recasting.
Xia Yimo was dissatisfied with playing
the second female lead in Mo Xiang,
so she jumped into the water
to threaten the crew.
It almost cost a life.
Am I not Xia Yimo?
No, you are Xue Keying.
You are the character persona
created by the actress Xia Yimo.
Whether Xia Yimo can
continue to play Xue Keying
determines whether you can
return to the world of the script.
What?
If Xia Yimo
stops playing Xue Keying,
you will disappear completely.